<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>

<content>

	<raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/marcus.jpg</image>
		<name>Marcus Dillistone</name>
		<titles>Film Director</titles>
        <credits>Royal Premiered and International Award winning film director. Associate Producer Music 2004 Athens Olympics Ceremonies.</credits>
		<testimonial>“I first met Paul when I was Associate Producer Music for the Athens 2004 Olympic Ceremonies. He subsequently worked for me on the soundtracks for two important global cinema projects - the results in each instance were world class. Paul is not only passionate, skilled, experienced and professional (with great ‘ears’), he is also totally committed to projects, unflappable and modest. Thus he is the perfect colleague and supplier.”

Marcus Dillistone - Film Director, Glory Film Co
</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/lee.jpg</image>
		<name>Lee Groves</name>
		<titles>Audio Engineer/Producer</titles>
        <credits>Black Eyed Peas, Craig David, Enya, Gwen Stefani, Janet Jackson, Marilyn Manson, Shaggy, Vanessa Carlton and many more!</credits>
		<testimonial>"I've used Paul Stefanidis and Viking Lounge Mastering several times on projects that I have produced and mixed. I have to say the results have always been fantastic. Paul has always been very fast, efficient and open to any changes that I've needed. Put simply: if you want your stuff to sound better, send it to Paul. I can wholeheartedly recommend his excellent service."

Lee Groves</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/trevor.jpg</image>
		<name>Trevor Steele</name>
		<titles>Audio Engineer/Producer</titles>
        <credits>Escape Club, Westlife, Popstars, Dirty Little Secret, ALittle Bit More, Colourblind and many more for major labels.</credits>
		<testimonial>"Paul has brought a welcome International professionalism to Sydney. No longer do I have to send tracks overseas to get the illusive final sound that I've been searching for and that Paul somehow effortlessly manages to achieve. I would recommend him to put the final gloss on  your record, no matter what style of music it is."

Trevor Steel - Sunday Morning Records</testimonial>
        
    </raves>
	
	<raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/porteils.jpg</image>
		<name>Craig Porteils</name>
		<titles>Audio Engineer/Producer</titles>
        <credits>Cher, Guns n Roses, Fleetwood Mac, Rod Stewart, Ozzy Osbourne, Terence Trent Darby, Dieisel, Wendy Matthews , Shortstack.</credits>
		<testimonial>I have worked with Paul at his studio, Viking Lounge Mastering, many times and always found it a complete pleasure. I believe Paul has the best ears in the industry for mastering. After Paul has worked on my mixes he puts that finishing touches on them that bring the mixes up to a new level. Paul treats each mix individually, giving the best treatment for the genre of music it is. 
Now that I have Paul for my mastering engineer I will look no further.

Craig Porteils - Short Stack, The Jefferson, Shannon Noll, Guy Sebastion</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/ash.jpg</image>
		<name>Ash Maklad</name>
		<titles>Engineer/Producer</titles>
        <credits>Young Divas, Mandi Jarry, Phil Burton/Human Nature, Courtney Act, Josh Quong Tart / Lemon Tart, The Moogies, Erika Heynatz, Papa Vs. Pretty,  Jo Elms</credits>

		<testimonial>"Paul at Vikings amazing attention to detail gives my mixes the shine that I’ve experienced from no other"	
	
Ash Maklad - Ash Maklad.com</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

	<raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/eddie.jpg</image>
		<name>Eddie Said/Rok Coalition</name>
		<titles>Producer/Writer/Remixer</titles>
        <credits>Westlife, Ricki-Lee, Short Stack, Amber, Paulini, Jon Stevens, Tina Cousins, Kate DeAraugo, Deni Hines.</credits>
		<testimonial>“Paul is the consummate professional with a personality to match his mastering genius. Viking Lounges mastering process is precise and also flexible giving my mixes the clarity and the kick in the head that want to hear from the music I produce. Working with Paul is not just an in and out procedure but an all-encompassing enjoyable experience. I’m definitely locked into Viking Lounge and would absolutely recommend Pauls mastering talents to all who want an international sonic without the hype!”

Eddie Said - Animal Music
 		</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/dolce.jpg</image>
		<name>Michael Dolce</name>
		<titles>Session Guitarist/Musical Director</titles>
        <credits>Roachford, Delta Goodrem, Ricki Lee, Brian McFadden, Natalie Bassingthwighte, The Young Divas, Jessica Mauboy, Amiel, Deni Hines</credits>
		<testimonial>“...all I can say is ,you are world class mate, the way you approached and mastered my album and the passion you showed was something I never experienced from any other engineer, and its proving to be a massive talking point amongst all listeners especially muso’s who always pay attention to detail...”

Michael Dolce
 		</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/frank.jpg</image>
		<name>Frank Colaiacolo</name>
		<titles>BDM and Director</titles>
        <credits>Business Development and Proprietor Sonic Factory Rehearsal and recording Studios Sydney.</credits>
		<testimonial>"NIght and day! Where once there was only darkness now only light shines through! In all seriousness, this is the only way that I can describe Paul at Viking Lounge Mastering. For many yeras, mastering was a hit and miss affair filled with many expensive disappointments. Well, that's in the past, I now have the golden ears of Paul Stefanidis taking care of business and I will never look back! I highly recommend Paul; he is truly a master of his art."
		
Frank Colaiacolo - Sonic Factory Studios</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/mojada.jpg</image>
		<name>Mojada</name>
		<titles>Sydney Independent band</titles>
        <credits>Organic funk rock outfit Mojada - the perfect new name for the groovy 4 piece from Sydney’s Bondi Beach.</credits>
		<testimonial>"Paul Stefanidis is a master of his craft, a true genius, who works with passion and dedication to a project that we have yet to come across. We have worked with some of the best mastering suites and engineers in the business and now knowing the results that are achievable at Viking Lounge, we would never go anywhere else. World class equipment, friendly atmosphere, and quality results right here at our doorstep. Thanks so much Paul for always delivering the best final touches to our music, and taking our songs to the next level."
		
Marco Yellin, Chad Kendrick and Wes Roy - Mojada J Dog Records
 		</testimonial>
        
    </raves>

    <raves>

        <image>images/thumbs/andy.jpg</image>
		<name>Andy Taylor</name>
		<titles>Audio Engineer/ Multimedia Producer</titles>
        <credits>Live/system engineer for Killing Heidi, Eskimo Joe, You Am I, The Next, Mach Pelican, Electric Eel Shock and countless others.</credits>
		<testimonial>"After 25 years of having my ears pounded in the live arena I have recently moved into the studio where I am free to try things a bit more experimental! I have recently completed a World Music album for Bengali singer Liton Sheikh and Paul has made what was a project studio recording that I was happy with into something truly World class! I am extremely pedantic about all things audio and have finally met someone that inspires and reinvigorates my passion for music. In fact, I was so impressed that I am now working for Paul as a Project Manager!"	
	
Andy Taylor - Studio Projects</testimonial>
        
    </raves>
				
</content>